Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending,
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, it's waiting
where we should be going, go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride away!
We're all together as well, so
let's just stay with us, son!
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one, go hey!
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see!
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Roger's treasure belongs to me!
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And then commence to
live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our mods will never give up There's a fire
in our dreams and you can never, never,
never, never stop it We
will be one, go ahead!
I've read your every thought
since the moment we met,
Blackleg Sanji No one can
hide from my all-seeing eyes.
I'd heard you had a soft spot for women,
but I didn't expect it to be that soft.
How pathetic.
You look like a mess, by the way.
Some prince charming,
covered in his own blood.
I almost pity you.
You're nothing but a
failure, Blackleg Sanji.
Be reasonable.
How would a worm like you win
the heart of a woman like me?
You're such a joke.
Yeah, you should have known our sis was
way too pretty to waste her time with you,
dumbass.
Violet, tell me it's not true.
You wouldn't do this.
Dude, get over it already.
She played you for a sap.
That's all there is to it.
They're lying.
Deep down, you have a beautiful,
good heart. I can tell.
How could you say such a thing?
After all this...
On your feet!
Someone must have put you up to this.
You don't even want to be a
part of it, do you, Violet?
You still think this is
some kind of love story?
Give me a break!
Idiot.
Damn!
I was pretty cold.
She kicked the crap out of him.
You're only pretending to care about me.
When really you're looking
for a chance to escape.
Do you honestly think you
can fool me with your lies?
i ate the glare glare
fruit thanks to that i've
become well quite
observant i can see through
anything now you men
are all liars let me see
inside your mind not
that anything in it will
be worth a damn why did
Straw Hat join up with
law what do they hope
to do what brings you to
dress rosa besides the
ceaser trade-off in green
bit answer my questions
and don't you dare lie
you don't have to speak if you won't
tell me i'll just look inside your mind
we'll locate all your crewmates
as well hey she's doing the pose
now
What's the matter?
Sis, what did you see?
Yeah, what's wrong?
So dirty!
Dirty!
His mind is totally pink!
I've never seen anything like it! What?
What are you up to, really?
What's your purpose here?
What could you possibly be
thinking about at a time like this?
I can't begin to fathom!
I'm thinking of you.
About the way you looked at me.
There is a man there—I
need you to kill for me.
I
knew that you weren't lying.
No
matter what you say.
No matter what anyone says.
I believe in you.
For
me, a girl's tears are always enough.
enough
This guy must think
he's in a romance novel.
I've never heard such cheesy crap.
I mean, there's desperate,
and then there's crazy.
Whatever.
He doesn't get it. Listen,
if you're done with this delusional moron,
we'd be more than happy
to finish him off for you.
This guy's worth $77 million.
Looks like it's the end
of Blackleg Sanjeev.
Prepare to die!
Karoo lagrima!
What's wrong, lady? Stop!
And I will!
You serious, you guys?
I get it now.
You were forced to work with
Doflamingo, weren't you?
You need to get away
from here, Black Lake.
And what about you? How could
I... I'm fine! Forget me!
Don't say that!
We know everything.
There's no way your plan will work.
You're walking straight into a trap.
You are trying to protect
one of your own enemies.
You're hopeless.
I don't know why you believed
in me, but thank you.
It made me happy.
I don't know the whole story here,
but if you don't want to work
for doflamingo, then leave!
You already attacked your own men—just
come with me, and we'll escape together!
Look into my eyes.
Black leg, from the moment you came here
with Caesar—your crew's fate was sealed.
Everything is following doflamingo's plan.
His plan, yes.
Gaze into my mind, and
you will understand?
will understand
Here's my memory of
Dress Rosa this morning.
Why, Your Majesty?
You can't really be quitting!
An explanation at least!
Please, Doflamingo!
What would ever make you
abdicate from the throne?
How annoying.
They should have arrived by now.
Warship?
They're heading for the harbor.
What?
I know that emblem, but
I can't place where?
That's from Cypher Pool.
It's just zero flag.
The government officials who work under
the world nobles—what are they doing here?
Citizens of dress rosa, I ask
you to remain calm and listen.
We've journeyed to your island to
address rumors concerning doflamingo's
abdication of the throne and
retirement from the seven warlords.
It was a false report, simply a mistake!
mistake
And to let the rest of the world know,
we'll be releasing an extra
edition of the newspaper at 3 p .m.
today, setting the record straight.
But it must be kept secret until then.
No one outside Dressrosa is to know.
Our top priority is for all
nations to keep living in peace,
as if nothing has happened.
why do i feel like everything just
got turned upside down the world
government i know the warlords are
powerful but that kind of influence is too
much one would think so please go
i'm too terrified of doflamingo to try
to leave dress rosa myself but maybe
you and your friends can get away
in time what the hell should I do wow
that's creepy were you hiding in the sand
listening in on us this entire time Nico
no this is just a clone of my body was that
song you were talking to on the transponder
snail just now first if this isn't your
actual body where are
you and the nose second
off if what Blackleg was saying is true.
The deal with Doflamingo is off.
What do you mean, off?
Then what about you handing me over?
Beniko, find the nose and let's
hurry up and get off this island.
One problem.
We're here on Greenbit, but Usopp
and I are currently both underground.
You what?
We fell into a bit of
trouble and got tied up.
But to make a long story
short, we're safe for now.
We can't help you, but if you're
going to escape, go without us.
When we get the opportunity, we'll leave
and catch up with you at the harbor.
Okay, got it.
No, not the Navy!
Here he comes.
I wish you luck.
Right back at ya.
Joker!
Hey, Lord.
I hate to admit it, but
you've managed to impress me.
Must have taken some effort to get
an actual Navy Admiral to show up.
And since I'm no longer a warlord,
I'm really shaking in my boots.
You're a damn liar!
now it's time all competitors in block c
have taken the stage 139 warriors in total
it's our third battle
royale of the day who
will be the last one standing in the ring
How'd you get down to the ring
without me seeing you get back here
You're inflecting are you trying
to get down on the hands me?
Let's do this!
An extra addition?
It must be a correction or something.
What is this garbage?
Captain, you need to see this! What is it?
It's big news about Doflamingo. Huh?
It was all a mistake?
This doesn't make any sense.
How could it be just an error?
You use the authority
of the world government
for some trick You
spread a false story and
to see people all over
the whole damn world
just to gain an advantage
over our small group
haven't you ever seen a magic show
the greatest delusions are often
pulled off with the simplest of
tricks law everyone always says well
that's ridiculous but it's the rigidity
of the mind assuming no one would
go to such lengths that creates the
blind spot in humans you're just a
pirate it doesn't matter if you're
one of the seven warlords it doesn't
even matter that you're a king you
don't have that much influence to make
everyone believe in an illusion to
lie to the whole world that power
doesn't exist and there's no one alive
who could ever pull it off that is
except for the celestial dragons you don't
know as much about
joker's past as you should
and you're going to pay with
your life for that ignorance
Don't tell me, you're a...
It's too complicated to explain right now.
No secret.
I just really wanted to kill you.
Joker!
Make him pay for this! Save me!
There's no way in hell you're
getting Caesar back now!
You and I had an agreement!
You can't just do what you want!
The deal's off, Doflamingo!
You're gonna regret this decision!
Hey, moron!
Just because you're screwed doesn't
mean you have to drag me down with you!
We've hardly spoken in ten
years, and this is how you act?
Treat your old boss nicer, won't you, Law?
Caesar is very valuable to me.
I need to have him back.
Isho, it would appear that Lyle brought
Caesar Clown here for a trade-off.
Ah, the scientist that caused
the poison gas incident.
A heinous crime.
Still, we'll see.
If he works for one of the seven
warlords, he'll get amnesty.
Tricky.
Hello there.
You're the famous vice-admiral who got
recruited in the World Military Draft,
aren't you?
Fujitoro, was it?
They say you and Vice
Admiral Ryokyugyu are both
forces to be reckoned
with on the battlefield.
Sir, you flatter me.
You can spare me the humble act.
Then I'll be frank.
I'm having some trouble
unraveling the situation.
You see, I don't have much
experience as a Marine,
so I don't want to make
any baseless accusations.
But it seems to me, as a warlord,
you're doing some things that step
outside of your boundaries just a bit.
For example,
the fellow over there just referred to you
as Joker, a rather troubling implication.
If you want to dig into my past, you'd
better be willing to get your hands dirty.
because it'll take a mountain
of evidence to topple me.
Speaking of naughty warlords,
what's the Navy going to do about law?
You're referring to the news about his
alliance with the infamous pirate Straw Hat.
If the reports are true,
then I'm afraid he's guilty.
So tell me: law, is he simply
your subordinate or is he an ally?
And you're guilty—what comes
next depends on your answer.
If you betrayed your position.
position will have to arrest both you
and the Straw Hats for your crimes.
What kind of half-assed decision is that?
All he has to do is lie and
you let him go scot-free?
My plan fell completely apart.
The Navy shows up and now I'm the target.
I can't let the team in
Dressrosa be affected by this.
I'm going to have to
make a stand on my own.
Lying won't help. It's true!
The Straw Hats aren't working under me!
We're equals in this alliance!
Just can't take the easy way, can you?
Well, that's it.
Your title is revoked.
But that might not be the
only headline tomorrow.
No way.
Meteor? That...
that can't be right!
That's a bit overkill, don't
you think? It's a meteor!
One more gazillion!
Go!
It's not here.
I can't see what I'm saying.
Happened where's he?
Show Joker seems they survived
though I can't
say how the.
Only thing left are the spots
they're standing on is this?
How the Navy acts.
Now show some restraint—are you insane?
Even a blind man won't miss
with an attack that big!
Ah, pardon me now!
Law, you're a criminal; therefore,
I'll be arresting you now. I
was
falling
in love.
Oh ain't that sweet?
Oh hey, I think I can find the
factory—easy for real, yep.
Problem is we can't just wreck it.
wreck it Get the whole ass out of here.
It's gonna be a whole thing.
A whole big thing.
Hey, you filthy little thief!
I told you we don't take credit!
Somebody stop that toy!
He took my burgers and didn't pay!
We'll be lucky just to
make it out alive now.
Yeah, I heard about Doflamingo's trap.
Man, we walked right into that one.
But just cause our fancy
plan went off the rails
doesn't mean we can't do some
damage while we're in town.
I got something brewing here that
might salvage this operation.
Yeah, it's complicated.
Just meet me at the flower
field and we'll work things out.
What the hell is that place anyway?
It sounds like something
out of a fairy tale.
By the way, I'm getting
worried about Nami. Come on.
Nami's tough as nails.
She'll be fine.
Have some faith.
Besides, she got broken
monster chopper with her too.
Uh, something up?
What are they watching there?
That's green.
They broadcast from the Coliseum.
The newcomer Luffy is putting
on a spoiler show today!
Love that beard!
He's small, but quick!
Franky, I found Luffy, and he's, uh...
Yeah, he's fighting in
some big tournament.
I forgot to tell you that.
Why didn't you do anything to stop him?
You can't trust him on his own!
Hey, you're in no position to judge me.
Blackleg, I have to get out of here.
They're coming for me.
My men.
You and your crew are trying to get
to Doflamingo's secret factory, right?
I have a map.
It's disguised.
It looks like a toy house on the exterior.
But that's your target.
No, you can't.
If you help me this much,
there's no turning back.
It's too late. I'm doomed.
It seems the executives already
know that I betrayed the family.
Violet, listen.
The Western Harbor.
You can meet me there.
Just stay hidden and wait for me.
That's our cruise rendezvous point.
I swear, I'll get you out, no
matter what the cost may be.
Hopeless.
You're just hopeless.
Pardon me, sir! Please fight!
Don't be hopeless!
Way to ruin the mood!
Where'd you come from?
Violet, wait!
Hurry! Defeat them!
Don't move!
Amazing!
They're just thugs. Why'd you need me?
They are holding my dear friend Congeno
hostage, so I was rendered helpless.
Speaking of which, I am
in dire need of your aid.
We must make haste to the toy house.
I have heard word that this is where
the fiends are holding Congeno,
but I don't know the way.
What the heck's going on up there?
It must be long.
This sucks!
If the roof caves in, then
we're all going to die!
Whoa!
Even the hero is scared now?
Kidding?
That earthquake was caused by me.
Or my Haki?
Haki?
That's how you beat up all 50 ,000 of those
bad guys back on Fishman Island, right?
So awesome!
That's our hero!
You're so strong, you can
shake the whole kingdom, huh?
Try this, hero!
A delicious gift!
A big piece of fighting fish!
They're like goldfish, only angry!
Those big guys? Yep!
Wow!
Didn't think it'd be so good!
It's almost as tasty as Sea King, which
I dine on all the time, of course.
I see.
So they're the ones who nab
that thing back on the bridge.
These little guys must be crazy strong.
Glad they're on my side.
Since we're small,
just one of those fighting fish could feed
the whole kingdom for
a month or even more.
You big people have to
eat an awful lot, though.
That must be a real pain sometimes.
Huh?
For Lufilon and my Ushalon fighting
force, a fish like this as just a snack.
What's Usaland?
That statue.
Look familiar to ya?
From that picture book
we read back in Jaya.
Leo, is that... Noland? Uh-huh.
I see, of course.
You know him, don't you?
He was the big person botanist who came
to visit our kingdom 400 years ago.
Our hero!
Back then, there were a bunch
of bad guys messing up our home,
but Noland rushed to the aid of
our ancestors and saved the day!
We'll never forget the debt we owe to
Noland, no matter how many years pass.
The Tumtada will always honor him!
When Ursuline mentioned the hero's name
and told us he was one of his descendants,
I just...
I was so overwhelmed! No! I
mean it! Look at my helmet!
It's shaped like a chestnut,
just like his head! He's right!
A chestnut head!
We tied you up! It's awful!
I am so sorry! You're shameless.
Don't complain, it saved you too!
Just keep quiet, enjoy the feast,
and then we'll get out of here.
Truly, it must be an act of
fate that brought you here.
And today, no less.
Yes, I agree.
After 400 long years have passed, a
legendary hero comes before us once again.
on the very day that we vowed
to go to war against Doflamingo!
Lucelyn,
after you finish eating,
we'll take the underground passage
to the flower field and prepare.
Now's the time!
The captain and his Rick royal army
are waiting for us in Dressrosa,
where the final battle
will be waged. Yeah!
Please, take the lead.
Usher us to freedom!
Together, we'll crush the
Don Quixote family! Yeah!
With Usaland, we're invincible!
Yeah!
Give him a cheer!
Usaland, yeah!